Good
morning guys, happy Monday.
Today is the first day of my day in the week vlog and I thought
you know what?
No, I'm not doing an intro.
I think intros can be kind of annoying.
So we're just starting the video.
No intro needed.
I'm walking.
Whoa, I'm out of breath.
Today I'm starting out the day walking to meet my friend for coffee.
Actually, a lot of you guys know her.
It's my friend Liz.
She's one of my really good friends here And we haven't like had a coffee
date in a really long time.
We've both just been really busy So we like scheduled this in advance.
So we're gonna meet at our favorite place.
It's the Brandy Cafe
Hey guys, Liz and I just got our coffee Coffee.
Guys, so two things changed.
I went lighter with my hair and Liz went darker.
Hey, we're back.
Guys, so this is what we did in the coffee shop.
Liz had a great idea.
My coffee was so sweet.
They put way too much vanilla in it.
She hadn't ordered hers yet.
She was like, okay, I'm gonna get a regular coffee with no sweetener and then
we're gonna mix them together.
It was like an experiment.
It was.
Really smart.
But the trick is to not, which I saw TikTok on this, but not to
pour the ice out.
Like you have to drain it.
In separate cups?
separate cups and then mix them and then we fixed the problem yeah so now
we have good coffees that aren't too sweet that was the salulu
okay guys i'm back in my apartment i had so much fun with liz this
morning we just had a cute little girls morning.
Honestly it's like such a nice Monday morning.
I don't usually like do that so I've been home for a couple hours just
working on my laptop.
I'm about to go print out some things for Ophelia with our summer launch coming
on Thursday so I need to go there but first I want to make a
smoothie because I am getting a little hungry.
You guys know my smoothie recipe by now is pretty much the same.
I was at lunch with my managers recently and they were talking about how much
collagen changed their life and they really educated me and inspired me to start taking
it.
So that is the one addition to my smoothie that I've been doing recently.
I got the ones from Vital Proteins and it is so good and I can't
notice a difference.
So for me, it works.
Anyways, I do need to quickly go print those things for the Ophelia cards that
we're going to be putting in our summer orders.
So I'm going to try to drink this quick, grab my stuff, and then walk
because I think it's like a 25 minute walk for me.
hi pookies i'm back wow should i start calling you guys that i went and
i got the prints for my ophelia drop on sunday on sunday it's on thursday
i got at least the tester prints for now i wanted to get specific cards
for our summer collection because i just thought it'd be really fun to switch it
up since these are our summer pieces and I want to put one of these
in every order.
So this is how they came out.
We took this photo and I took this on my iPhone actually.
I loved it.
The second I took this photo at the beach I knew that this was going
to be the photo of all the ones we took in our shoot.
So I ended up getting a few for now.
On the back it has a little note with a discount code that I'm not
going to show because it's if you order.
Sorry gatekeeping.
I did that and then on my way back I decided to stop at the
grocery store because I have no food.
Like I'm not even gonna be dramatic.
I think I have a bag of chocolate chips.
That's about it.
I'm gonna do a little haul of what I got because I love grocery hauls
because I like just getting inspo for meals.
You guys know it's kind of hard for me sometimes to think of meal ideas.
So I'm just gonna show you a few of the things that I got.
First things first, my priorities.
Strawberry lemonade.
This is so good.
And banana chips which I already started eating.
I want to make chicken stir-fry tonight.
So I got some bell peppers for that.
Obviously I got chicken.
I also I got some broccoli for that.
Other things include bread, oats, because I want to make overnight oats.
I was literally in Trader Joe's looking up breakfast ideas because when I find a
breakfast I like, I will eat that every day for probably about three months until
I'm sick of it.
And then I move on and I discard it.
The current breakfast has been yogurt with berries, which is good.
It's been too long.
You know, this is a cyclical thing.
The cycle is done with my yogurt.
I've developed an aversion to it now because I've had it so much and I
need to find my next breakfast.
I hope that I like this.
I'm sure I will.
I used to eat these often.
Overnight oats with some berries and nuts.
I got chia seeds for that too and some granola because I thought maybe I'd
put granola on top.
I also got these sunflower seed butter cups.
They're really good.
Probably gonna have one now.
I actually like the peanut butter ones better.
don't get these okay well fail i got more peanut butter because i ran out
and some fries and lastly stir fry sauce for my stir fry that i'm gonna
make for dinner tonight that's my little haul um i actually i actually don't know
what to do um i'm gonna call my mom
so i did make my dinner i made a chicken fajita rice bowl i don't
know if that's technically what this is but i've been making taco bowls and i'm
kind of getting sick of them so i decided to make chicken instead with some
pepper and onions and then i just threw in some broccoli and rice and teriyaki
sauce, which I want more of.
We all know I'm not the best chef.
I'm not even a chef.
I'm just trying to survive.
You know, cooking is new to me.
I really didn't cook in college at all.
Post-grad now, I still didn't cook last year.
I had no kitchen.
So this is like my first time cooking consistently and I'm learning, you know.
I think my biggest weakness is that I take forever.
Like this took me an hour.
It will probably take most people 20 minutes.
So that does frustrate me.
I have to figure out something because I could not be spending this much time.
I made leftovers for tomorrow.
I'm gonna eat this and then watch the game.
I'm a really big Timberwolves fan.
Honestly, my perfect night.
Good morning, guys.
It's the next day.
I'm kind of in like a sad mood.
I'm one of those people who the weather really affects my mood.
And today is extremely gloomy and rainy.
Especially on days like this, I need to get out of my apartment and like
force myself out.
Because it just like makes me mentally feel a little better.
I was going to go to Central Park today.
with some friends but that is obviously not happening anymore so instead I'm gonna go
to a cute coffee shop which I know I always go to I feel like
that's just appropriate for rainy days to go to a coffee shop also to make
me feel better I want to get dressed and ready and put on a cute
little outfit I have a few options of things the one thing I know for
certain is I'm gonna be wearing this bag and I'm gonna kind of revolve my
outfit around this because I love it and I just got it and coach is
actually sponsoring this video so thank you so much to them that is actually a
dream for me.
I have them on my vision board guys.
I put them on there as a goal of a brand to work with.
It came true guys.
This is your sign to really make your vision board.
Let me show you.
This is my vision board and there is coach.
You guys already know I love coach.
This is the coach terry bag and this is such a beautiful bag because I
like how the coach logo is so subtle and I also really like the silver
hardware.
I've been really into silver recently and I also like this one specifically because it
is so neutral.
It just like would go with any outfit.
Let me try them on and see what we like.
For pants, I'm thinking these low-waisted flared black pants.
Okay, here's the look so far.
I don't know what I think about this.
I like it.
I want to try this coat and see what we think.
Okay, this is the second option.
I don't know what I think, but I feel like I can do a little
better.
All right, guys.
Outfit is complete.
I ended up sticking with mixing black and brown.
I added some silver jewelry today also.
I wanted to keep it consistent with my bag that has silver hardware.
You guys know my favorite boots of all time are these.
I love how this look came together, and my coach bag goes so perfectly with
it.
I do like with coach that I can either dress up outfit or dress it
down with the bag.
Thank you.
🎵
Good morning, guys.
You may be wondering what is the occasion for the matcha and the flowers.
I'm getting my friend matcha and flowers for her birthday.
So I woke up this morning.
I was texting her roommate because I need to drop it off, hopefully before she
wakes up.
After I dropped off her little birthday surprise, I had a lot of work to
do because Ophelia launched our summer collection on this day.
We were launching at 11 a.m.
and I think I'm filming this around 9.
I just had a few finishing touches and things I needed to do on the
website and it was really successful.
As I'm talking to you guys right now, we sold out of almost everything.
I think we're planning on a restock right around when this video goes up.
Thank you guys if you have supported Ophelia.
It means the world to me.
But after it launched, I took the train to go to a meeting I had
planned with my managers.
Okay guys, a little update.
So I finished working at the coffee shop and my summer collection just went live
for Ophelia.
It's doing really well.
I'm not really the best with website stuff and my assistant's out of town so
I was a little worried about it but it ended up going live really smoothly
and now I'm on my way to a little meeting with my manager.
I just took the subway.
I'm running a little late so I feel a little bad about that.
We're getting lunch at this Italian restaurant called La Cora Bianca which I don't think
I've been to before.
Wow my heels are so loud.
They're very loud.
Oh my gosh, guys.
I am so car sick right now.
I had my little lunch meeting with my managers and then I Ubered to Brooklyn,
which was like a 20 minute Uber because I have an event with Drunk Elephant,
which I'm really excited.
It's kind of like a, they call it, I think a masterclass.
The Ubers here are like so jerky and it makes me feel sick every single
time and this time was especially bad so before I go in I'm like standing
outside because I need to recover and help my nausea to go away.
I hate being carsick.
I do feel like I'm gonna be ill all day.
update my skin is glowing that was so fun i've never done like a master
class like that with the brand i've seen so many brands put on little events
like that and i've always wanted to go sorry guys i feel like i've been
vlogging poorly today which we all knew one of these days would have that it
just seems to always be that way i've just been running around like all day
so i'm in the uber to my friend's birthday the same friend that i dropped
off the coffee and flowers for this morning.
She's having like a little birthday dinner lunch.
Uh, is there anything else I have to say?
No, fine.
That's it.
Okay.
Bye.
Say to you.
Good morning.
I just woke up.
Why would I even say that?
Like I clearly just woke up.
Like I don't need to say that.
You guys can tell.
I have to post a video, I have to post two videos, and then I
have to submit a third video to a brand.
And I'm pretty behind on my editing, so I'm basically just going to be at
my computer all day long.
Big thing for me though on days like this, when I'm just going to be
on my computer for so much of it, is that I just need to get
out of my apartment.
It's like the social stimulation, even if I'm not speaking to people though, because obviously
I'm working majority of the time on my laptop but just like being around people
for me like mentally is so important and I've been like this since I was
like 17 I remember editing videos or just doing schoolwork and homework and I'd always
prefer to like leave my house and do it somewhere else obviously not all the
time but especially on long days like this it just helps to like break up
my day being around people like makes me feel less alone I guess especially because
I live alone and I like work alone as As much as I love to
be alone, and we talk about that on here a lot, I do think it's
important for me to just get out and socialize and just be around people and
coexist with other people.
So let's get ready.
And it's 7 a.m., so we're getting an early start.
I just realized I never made my overnight oats.
I actually forgot about them.
I have no words.
Like, I can't believe I did that.
I was hyping them up for you guys.
I do make the best avocado toast, though.
My friends would say the same.
I've made avocado toast for two of my friends, and they loved it.
I've really perfected my recipe.
It's obviously not that hard, but I'm very proud of it.
It's like the one thing I can make
I'm with Nikki.
Say hi introduce yourself.
Hi, I'm Nekki.
We're having an editing date, working together because we both need to edit like all
the time.
I've been here since like literally 8am and we're just working together.
Oh my god, my neighbor below me is so loud.
I can always hear his conversations in detail.
I can hear everything he's talking about.
I feel like things I shouldn't know.
I have been home for the past five hours since I left the coffee shop.
I've just been in my bed laying editing my vlog and I just posted it
so I feel really good about that but I literally had nothing to vlog because
I was sitting in silence for five hours.
Right now I'm going to be packing orders for Ophelia, my jewelry brand.
I think I talked about this earlier in the week but we launched our summer
collection and I want to pack some of the orders.
We do everything out of my apartment which is kind of crazy but I wanted
to do things like fully myself to learn all aspects of the business from the
little things to the big things so I'm gonna pack some of the orders from
our summer collection that just launched and I love it and I think it sold
out or some of the pieces sold out already and it just launched so that's
crazy I love you guys I think we're gonna be restocking hopefully next week this
is the setup we have right now I laid everything out really aesthetically just for
a photo for the instagram but i'm gonna start packing
okay guys roughly an hour and a half later i finished the orders for today
they're right here all wrapped and ready to go to be shipped out tomorrow.
I am...
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
Probably go to bed soon.
So that took actually longer than I thought.
I always underestimate the time on everything and I need to get better at that.
So good night.
Good morning guys.
It's a good day because I remembered finally to make my overnight oats last night.
I literally got into bed, was about to go to sleep, and then I remembered
suddenly that I needed to make my overnight oats.
So it's really easy.
It's basically same parts oats and milk and then some peanut butter and honey and
then I just threw in some strawberries and granola on top.
Oh there's also chia seeds in here.
Um I'm gonna eat this in peace and enjoy the sun because the sun is
out.
I'm gonna get ready and then we'll figure out the day.
Okay guys I got dressed.
By the way, breakfast was so good.
That's my new hyper fixation breakfast.
I got this outfit shopping at the vintage shop by my apartment last week and
I love it.
I am leaving for Alaska next week.
So random.
I know people are gonna be like, why are you going to Alaska?
Honestly, my dad and I just wanted to take a trip together.
We've always talked about going to Alaska.
The nature, it looks beautiful there and it's supposed to be a good time of
year to go.
It is going to be a little chillier than I anticipated though.
So I want to go to Brandy to grab a few warmer pieces of clothing
that are so cute.
I'm thinking like a crew neck or like a zip up hoodie.
I'm going to do that and then when I get back later I think I'm
going to pack.
Brandy kind of sucked today at least in my opinion it did.
I just was kind of underwhelmed but just as I gave up hope on my
way out I saw this zip up.
It's actually pretty thick which is kind of what influenced me to get this because
I do think it will keep me warm and then i went home and i
packed so that was my week in the life vlog i hope you guys liked
watching stay tuned for the next video i'm so excited it's gonna be one of
my favorites and i'll see you next week love you guys